Guide to the Martha Wilson Papers, 1950-2019 (bulk 1964-2006) MSS.175
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Correspondence, 1964-2013; 172383
  - Subseries A: General Correspondence, 190087
    - Manhattan Neighborhood Network, 1994-1998; 206188 (Box 14, Folder 140)
    - Manhattan Youth Recreation, 1998; 206189 (Box 14, Folder 141)
    - Manos, Kenna, 1976-1979; 206190 (Box 14, Folder 142)
    - Mantara, undated; 206191 (Box 14, Folder 143)
    - Manufacturers Hanover Trust, 1985, undated; 206192 (Box 14, Folder 144)
    - Maran, 1991; 206193 (Box 14, Folder 145)
    - Maran, Maeve and Wayne Pambianchi, 1980-2002; 206194 (Box 14, Folder 146)
    - Maran, Maeve, 1984-1992; 206195 (Box 14, Folder 147)
    - Marc, undated; 206196 (Box 14, Folder 148)
    - Margaret, undated; 206197 (Box 14, Folder 149)
    - [Margaret], 1974; 206198 (Box 14, Folder 150)
    - Marge and Sandy, 1988; 206199 (Box 14, Folder 151)
    - Marian, undated; 206201 (Box 14, Folder 152)
    - Marian, 1972, undated; 206202 (Box 14, Folder 153)
    - Mark, 2005; 206203 (Box 14, Folder 154)
    - Markisch, Sven, 2006; 206204 (Box 14, Folder 155)
    - Marim, undated; 206205 (Box 14, Folder 156)
    - Martha, undated; 206206 (Box 14, Folder 157)
    - Martin, Pedro, 1987; 206207 (Box 14, Folder 158)
    - Martinazzoli, Luca, 2007; 206208 (Box 14, Folder 159)
    - Martinez, Daniel Joseph, 1999; 206209 (Box 14, Folder 160)
    - Marty, 1981-1982; 206210 (Box 14, Folder 161)
    - Marty and Glenn, undated; 206211 (Box 14, Folder 162)
    - Marty and Randy, undated; 206212 (Box 14, Folder 163)
    - Mary, 1989-1995, undated; 206213 (Box 14, Folder 164)
    - Mary, undated; 206214 (Box 14, Folder 165)
    - Mary and Tom, undated; 206215 (Box 14, Folder 166)
    - Mary Theresa, undated; 206216 (Box 14, Folder 167)
    - Matherson, Nichelle/College Art Association, 1999; 206217 (Box 14, Folder 168)
    - Matta, Susan, 1975; 206218 (Box 14, Folder 169)
    - Mattern, Yvette, undated; 206219 (Box 14, Folder 170)
    - Maureen, 1987; 206220 (Box 14, Folder 171)
    - Mavor, Anne, 1994-1996; 206221 (Box 14, Folder 172)
    - [Maubel], Carol, 2004; 206222 (Box 14, Folder 173)
    - Maya, 1989-2003, undated; 206223 (Box 14, Folder 174)
    - Mayer, Rosemary, undated; 206224 (Box 14, Folder 175)
    - Meier, Yvonne, 1995; 206228 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Melchert, Mary Ann and Jim, 1991-1996; 206229 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Melinda, 1992; 206230 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Melby, Julia/ Toledo Museum of Art, 2000-2001, undated; 206231 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Mendoza, Dorotea, 2008; 206232 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Mercer Union/Anette Larson, 1996; 206233 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Merchant, Shabnam, 2008; 206234 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Mercy, 1998-2002; 206235 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Meris, Doneley/HIV Arts Network, 1996; 206236 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Mermelstein, Jeff, undated; 206237 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Messinger, Ruth, 1989-1994; 206238 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Messner, Ann, 2003; 206239 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Mew. Tommy, 1976; 206240 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Meyer, Deborah, 1987-2002; 206241 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Meyers, Michael, 1981; 206242 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Michael, 1976; 206243 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Michael, undated; 206244 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Michael, 1979-1985, date illegible; 206245 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Michael, 1972-1982, undated; 206246 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence from Wilson to Michael, 1978-1980; 206247 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Mike, 1996; 206248 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Mike, 1996; 206249 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Miller, Jen, 2001; 206250 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Miller, Jennifer, 2005; 206251 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Miller, Larry V., 1975; 206252 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Miller-Keller, Andrea and Tony Keller, 1992-1996; 206253 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Mills, Chris, 2002; 206254 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Mills, Lynn, undated; 206255 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Milman, Estera, 1994; 206266 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Minarelli, Enzo, 2007; 206267 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Mira, undated; 206268 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Mitchell, 1981; 206269 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Mobley, Vanessa, 1998; 206270 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Mockman, Paul, 1990; 206271 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Mogul, Susan, 1981-2007, undated; 206272 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Mohammed, Centro di Comunicazione Ristretta, 1979; 206273 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Montgomery, Ken, 2006; 206274 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Moore, Alan, 2007, undated; 206275 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Moore, Frank, 1995-2001, undated; 206276 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Moore, George, 1997; 206277 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Moore, John, 2001; 206278 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Moore, Townie, 1975; 206279 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Monchik, Lauren/ Ms. Magazine, 1996; 206280 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Monsod, Trinket, 1987; 206281 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Montano, Linda, 1981-2000, undated; 206282 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Montclair State College/ Caron Van Gilder, 1987-1988; 206283 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Morello, Terry, undated; 206284 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Moren, Lisa, 2002; 206285 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Morgan, Carol, 1984; 206286 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Morin, France/ 49th Parallel, 1989; 206287 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Morrell, Pearl, 1990; 206288 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Morris, Catherine, 2005; 206289 (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - Morris, Nancie, 1978; 206290 (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Morris, Penny and Julie, 1997; 206291 (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Morris, Penny and Robert, 1977-2008, undated; 206292 (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - Morris, W.E., date illegible; 206293 (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - Morris-Martel, Gay and Emily, 1986-1990, undated; 206294 (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - Mosakowski, Susan, 2007; 206295 (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - Moss, Lawrence, 1995-2006; 206296 (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - Moss, Stanley, 1994; 206297 (Box 15, Folder 60)
    - Motson, Don, 1976-1986; 206298 (Box 15, Folder 61)
    - Mouraud, Tania, 1977; 206299 (Box 15, Folder 62)
    - Moya and Pink, undated; 206300 (Box 15, Folder 63)
    - Moya, S and E, undated; 206301 (Box 15, Folder 64)
    - Moynihan, Daniel P., 1995; 206302 (Box 15, Folder 65)
    - Muel, Susanne, 1990; 206303 (Box 15, Folder 66)
    - Mueller, Susanne, 1989; 206304 (Box 15, Folder 67)
    - Muller, Elizabeth, 1992; 206305 (Box 15, Folder 68)
    - Multiple names, 1982-2005, undated; 206306 (Box 15, Folder 69)
    - Multiple, Birthday Party, 1984; 206307 (Box 15, Folder 70)
    - The Municipal Art Society/ Gloria Troy, 1993-1994; 206308 (Box 15, Folder 71)
    - Munn, Norma P., 1990; 206309 (Box 15, Folder 72)
    - Munrre, Alexandra, 1990; 206310 (Box 15, Folder 73)
    - Murphy, Charlotte/ National Association of Artist's Organizations, 1985-1992; 206311 (Box 15, Folder 74)
    - Murphy, Pat, 1989; 206312 (Box 15, Folder 75)
    - Murphy, Suzanne, undated; 206313 (Box 15, Folder 76)
    - Murray, Ian, 1977; 206314 (Box 15, Folder 77)
    - Murrin, Tom, 1983-2002, undated; 206315 (Box 15, Folder 78)
    - Murthy, Sheelah, 2001; 206316 (Box 15, Folder 79)
    - The Muse Museum, 2000; 206317 (Box 15, Folder 80)
    - Myerson, Bess, 1986; 206318 (Box 15, Folder 81)
    - N, Jack and Alice, 1989; 206319 (Box 15, Folder 82)
    - Naidus, Beverly and Bob Spivey, 1995; 206320 (Box 15, Folder 83)
    - Nakka, Deborah, 1977; 206321 (Box 15, Folder 84)
    - Nancy, 1976; 206322 (Box 15, Folder 85)
    - Nao, 2003; 206323 (Box 15, Folder 86)
    - Nathan, undated; 206324 (Box 15, Folder 87)
    - Nathan and Genie, 1994; 206325 (Box 15, Folder 88)
    - National Assembly on Arts, Organizing and Environmental Justice, 1992; 206326 (Box 15, Folder 89)
    - National Association of Artists' Organizations, 1987-1989; 206327 (Box 15, Folder 90)
    - National Campaign for Freedom of Expression, 1992-1995; 206328 (Box 15, Folder 91)
    - National Coalition Against Censorship/Joan Borfin, 2004-2005; 206329 (Box 15, Folder 92)
    - National Cultural Alliance/ Able, Edward, Kathy Dwyer Southern, 1991; 206330 (Box 15, Folder 93)
    - National Endowmnet for the Arts, 1981-1987; 206331 (Box 15, Folder 94)
    - National Gallery of Canada, 1995; 206332 (Box 15, Folder 95)
    - National Studio Program, 1998; 206333 (Box 15, Folder 96)
    - National Visual Arts Guild/ Daniel Tisdale, 1998-2001; 206334 (Box 15, Folder 97)
    - Naylor, Penelope, 1984; 206335 (Box 15, Folder 98)
    - Neary, Scott, 1979; 206336 (Box 15, Folder 99)
    - Necol, Jane, 1997-2004; 206337 (Box 15, Folder 100)
    - [Nees], Susan, 1989; 206338 (Box 15, Folder 101)
    - Nemec, Vernita, 1985-1995; 206339 (Box 15, Folder 102)
    - Nesbett, Peter, 2007; 206340 (Box 15, Folder 103)
    - Neshat, Shirin, 1991-1993, undated; 206341 (Box 15, Folder 104)
    - Neu, Jim, 1986-1995; 206342 (Box 15, Folder 105)
    - The New Cinema, 1979; 206343 (Box 15, Folder 106)
    - New Jersey City University, 2006; 206351 (Box 15, Folder 107)
    - New Museum/ Sarah Farsad, 2000; 206352 (Box 15, Folder 108)
    - New Observations/ Erika Knerr, 1993, undated; 206353 (Box 15, Folder 109)
    - New School for Social Research, 1992-1994; 206354 (Box 15, Folder 110)
    - New York City Arts Coalition, 1988; 206355 (Box 15, Folder 111)
    - New York City Transit Authority, 1994; 206356 (Box 15, Folder 112)
    - New York Foundation for the Arts, 1985-2008; 206357 (Box 15, Folder 113)
    - New York Institute for the Humanities/ Aileen Ward, 1992-1995, undated; 206358 (Box 15, Folder 114)
    - New York State Council on the Arts, 2002-2003; 206359 (Box 15, Folder 115)
    - New York University, 2001; 206360 (Box 15, Folder 116)
    - New York University/ Faculty Resource Network, 2006; 206365 (Box 15, Folder 117)
    - New York University/ Gallatin Arts and Society Committee, 1992; 206366 (Box 15, Folder 118)
    - Newman, Amy, 1993; 206367 (Box 15, Folder 119)
    - Newman, Michael, 1988-1991, date illegible; 206368 (Box 10, Folder 120)
    - Newmark, Susan, 1996; 206369 (Box 10, Folder 121)
    - Nichio, Linda, 1986; 206370 (Box 15, Folder 122)
    - Nina, undated; 206371 (Box 15, Folder 123)
    - Nix, Marilyn, 1977-1994; 206372 (Box 15, Folder 124)
    - Noble, Sabine and Anja Mayer, undated; 206373 (Box 15, Folder 125)
    - Nolan, Janet, 1988-2004, undated; 206374 (Box 15, Folder 126)
    - Nolan, Patti, 1994; 206375 (Box 15, Folder 127)
    - North Miami Center of Contemporary Art/ Lou Anne Colodny, 1992; 206376 (Box 15, Folder 128)
    - Not in Our Name, undated; 206377 (Box 15, Folder 129)
    - Nova Scotia College of Art and Design, 1994-1995; 206378 (Box 15, Folder 130)
    - Novak, Barbara and Brian O'Doherty, 1984-1989; 206379 (Box 15, Folder 131)
    - Novak, Linda, 1983-1992; 206380 (Box 15, Folder 132)
    - Novelli, Patricia, 2005-2006; 206381 (Box 15, Folder 133)
    - Novey, Judith, 1983; 206382 (Box 15, Folder 134)
    - O., 1985; 206383 (Box 15, Folder 135)
    - O'brien, Mern/ Dalhousie University, 1994; 206384 (Box 15, Folder 136)
    - Obrien, Mark/ Davis, Polk and Wardwell, 1992; 206385 (Box 15, Folder 137)
    - O'Doherty, Barbara and Brian, 1990-2008; 206386 (Box 15, Folder 138)
    - O'Donghue/Caddy, 2005; 206387 (Box 15, Folder 139)
    - O'Donoghue, Carrie, 2004-2007; 206388 (Box 15, Folder 140)
    - Oerlemans, Marguerite, 1987; 206389 (Box 15, Folder 141)
    - O'Farrell, Dierdre, 1984; 206390 (Box 15, Folder 142)
    - O'Grady, Lorraine, 1989-2008; 206391 (Box 15, Folder 143)
    - Oji, Helen, 1991, undated; 206392 (Box 15, Folder 144)
    - Oleszko, Pat, 2004-2005; 206393 (Box 15, Folder 145)
    - Olin, Ferris, 2007; 206401 (Box 15, Folder 146)
    - Ontario Arts Council, 1994; 206402 (Box 15, Folder 147)
    - Ontario College of Art and Design/ J. Anthony Caldwell, 2006; 206403 (Box 15, Folder 148)
    - Ortiz, Raphael, 1988-1991, undated; 206404 (Box 15, Folder 149)
    - Osei-Boateng, Lillian, 2007; 206405 (Box 15, Folder 150)
    - O'Sullivan, Annie, 1983-2003; 206418 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Ott, James, 1967-1968, undated; 206419 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Ottergibbon, Kelly, Cole and Tom, 2002; 206420 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Owen, Taylor, 1993; 206421 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - P., Adam, undated; 206422 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - PS 122/ Dominick Balletta/ Anne Dennin, 2005; 206423 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Pace, Linda/Art Pace, 206424 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - The Page Museum, undated; 206425 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Painter, Dave and Betty Lou, 2000-2008, undated; 206426 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Palaia, Franc, 1987; 206427 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Palgrave MacMillan, 2006; 206428 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Pambianchi, 2000; 206429 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Park, Kyong, 2007; 206430 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Parker, William, 1992; 206431 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Parsons School of Design/ Jane Newl, 1997-1998; 206432 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Patricia, undated; 206433 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Patrick, undated; 206434 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Patrick, undated; 206435 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Patrick, undated; 206436 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Patti, 2003; 206437 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Paul, 1976; 206438 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Paul and Lynn, 1989; 206439 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Paulie, 1978; 206440 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Pavelić, Radovan, 2000; 206441 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Pederson, Ronald, 1980; 206442 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Peer, Linda, 1990, undated; 206443 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Peggy, undated; 206444 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Peierle, Julie and Ron, 1975-2002, undated; 206445 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Penney, Joseph/ Amigos de las Americas, 2005; 206446 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Pennsylvania Academy of Fine Arts/ Regina Neu, 1987; 206447 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Penny, 1988, undated; 206449 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Performance Studies international, 2005; 206450 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - [Perhi], 1990; 206451 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Perjovschi, Dan, 1999; 206452 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Perlmutter, David, 1998; 206453 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Perlmutter-Pilchik, Harriet, 1989; 206454 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Perry, 2002; 206455 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Perry, Sabra/ Ontological-Hysteric Theater, 1996; 206456 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Peter, 1976; 206457 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Peter, Ernest/ Avocus, 1995; 206458 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Peter Z., illegible; 206459 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Peters, Robert and Sarah Core, 1985; 206460 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Petit, Cecilia and Matthew Hall, 1995-2006, undated; 206461 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Pettitt, Peggy and Remy Tissier, undated; 206462 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - [Petusm], Ericka H., 1979-1981; 206463 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Pfaffman-Blieden, Molly, Scott, Phoebe and Max, 2001-2009, undated; 206464 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Phace, Hapi, 1995; 206465 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Phelan, Peggy, 2000; 206466 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Phil and Heth, 1968; 206467 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Philbin Ann, 1990-1998; 206468 (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Phillips, Alice, 1978; 206469 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Phillips, Patricia/SUNY New Paltz, 2006; 206470 (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Phillips, Peter, 1981; 206471 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Phillpot, Clive, undated; 206472 (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Pierrakos, Magdalen, 1978-1981, undated; 206473 (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - Piette/ Bennett, 1999; 206474 (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - Piette, Georges, 1991-2003, undated; 206475 (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - Pijuan, Angels Ribe, 2002; 206476 (Box 16, Folder 58)
    - Pilkington, Penny and Wendy Olsoff, undated; 206477 (Box 16, Folder 59)
    - Pindell, Howardena, undated; 206478 (Box 16, Folder 59)
    - Pilkington, Penny and Wendy Olsoff, undated; 206479 (Box 16, Folder 60)
    - Piper, Adrian, 1986-1987; 206480 (Box 16, Folder 61)
    - Pitman, Sandy, undated; 206481 (Box 16, Folder 62)
    - Pittore, Carlo, 1982-1985; 206482 (Box 16, Folder 63)
    - Platzker, David, 2007; 206483 (Box 16, Folder 64)
    - Plunkett, Em, undated; 206484 (Box 16, Folder 65)
    - The Poetry Mailing List, 1976; 206485 (Box 16, Folder 66)
    - Polak, Jenny, 2004-2005, undated; 206486 (Box 16, Folder 67)
    - Pollack, Barbara, 1987-1996, undated; 206490 (Box 16, Folder 68)
    - Ponton, Anita, 2001; 206491 (Box 16, Folder 69)
    - Poor, Penny, 1988; 206492 (Box 16, Folder 70)
    - Pope L., Willaim, 1994-1997, undated; 206502 (Box 16, Folder 71)
    - Porter, Marc, 1987; 206503 (Box 16, Folder 72)
    - Pottenger, Marty, 1988-1997; 206504 (Box 16, Folder 73)
    - Potter, Patricia, 2008; 206505 (Box 16, Folder 74)
    - Pou, Alyson, 1985-2003, undated; 206506 (Box 16, Folder 75)
    - Pratt, Christina, undated; 206507 (Box 16, Folder 76)
    - Preddy, Robby, 1996; 206508 (Box 16, Folder 77)
    - Pretto, Julian, 1976; 206509 (Box 16, Folder 78)
    - Primm, Sandy, 1978-1979, undated; 206510 (Box 16, Folder 79)
    - Printed Matter, 1983; 206511 (Box 16, Folder 80)
    - Prokell, Jamie/ School of Visual Arts, undated; 206558 (Box 16, Folder 81)
    - Protein-Aide, 1986; 206559 (Box 16, Folder 82)
    - Pryor, Sally, 1986; 206560 (Box 16, Folder 83)
    - Publishers Clearing House/ Attorney General, 1997-1998; 206561 (Box 16, Folder 84)
    - Pulliam, Linda J., 1996; 206562 (Box 16, Folder 85)
    - Puryear, Martin, 1989; 206563 (Box 16, Folder 86)
    - Quinn, Barbara, 1977-2009, undated; 206564 (Box 16, Folder 87)
    - Quinn, Patty, 1982; 206565 (Box 16, Folder 88)
    - [Quna], Silene, 2008; 206566 (Box 16, Folder 89)
    - R, 1991; 206567 (Box 16, Folder 90)
    - R., Susan, 1976; 206568 (Box 16, Folder 91)
    - Rabbers, Kathy, 1998; 206569 (Box 16, Folder 92)
    - Rachel, undated; 206570 (Box 16, Folder 93)
    - Ragona, Melissa, 2005-2006; 206571 (Box 16, Folder 94)
    - Rahman, Afshaan/ White Box, 2005; 206572 (Box 16, Folder 95)
    - Rahmani, Aviva, undated; 206573 (Box 16, Folder 96)
    - Rahan, undated; 206574 (Box 16, Folder 97)
    - Ramirez, Hertha, 1979-1986; 206575 (Box 16, Folder 98)
    - Ramirez, Paul Henry, 1995; 206576 (Box 16, Folder 99)
    - Ramirez, Yasmin and William Lipton, 2008; 206577 (Box 16, Folder 100)
    - Randazzo, Michael/ New School University, 2001; 206578 (Box 16, Folder 101)
    - Randy and Cathy, 1989; 206579 (Box 16, Folder 102)
    - Randy, Marty and Gage, 1996; 206580 (Box 16, Folder 103)
    - Rankin, Gratia, 1978; 206581 (Box 16, Folder 104)
    - Ransick, Robert, 1994; 206582 (Box 16, Folder 105)
    - Raphael, 1992; 206583 (Box 16, Folder 106)
    - Raphael, Shirley, undated; 206584 (Box 16, Folder 107)
    - Rappaport, Richard, 1989; 206585 (Box 16, Folder 108)
    - Rauschenbusch, Stephanie, 1999; 206586 (Box 16, Folder 109)
    - Raven, Arlene, 1978-1984; 206587 (Box 16, Folder 110)
    - Ray, Jeff/The Lab, 2005; 206811 (Box 16, Folder 111)
    - Read, James, 1968; 206812 (Box 16, Folder 112)
    - Reagan, Nancy, undated; 206813 (Box 16, Folder 113)
    - Rebecca and Susan, undated; 206814 (Box 16, Folder 114)
    - Rebollo, Fernando, 1982-1998, undated; 206815 (Box 16, Folder 115)
    - Reder, Ronnie, 1975; 206816 (Box 16, Folder 116)
    - Redmond, Layne, 1978-1999; 206817 (Box 16, Folder 117)
    - Reece, 1998; 206818 (Box 16, Folder 118)
    - Reedy, Carlyle, 1998; 206819 (Box 16, Folder 119)
    - Reichard, Stephen (friends and family), undated; 206820 (Box 16, Folder 120)
    - Reid, undated; 206821 (Box 16, Folder 121)
    - Reid, Susan, 1967-1969; 206822 (Box 16, Folder 122)
    - Reifel, Noel, 1991; 206823 (Box 16, Folder 123)
    - Reingold, Babs, 2003; 206824 (Box 16, Folder 124)
    - Reis, Victoria/ National Association of Artists' Organizations, 1996; 206825 (Box 16, Folder 125)
    - Reitmaier, Heidi, undated; 206826 (Box 16, Folder 126)
    - Research Assessment Exercise 2001, 2001-2002; 206827 (Box 16, Folder 127)
    - Resnicow Schroeder Associates, undated; 206828 (Box 16, Folder 128)
    - Rensselar Polytechnic/ Igor Vamos, 2001; 206829 (Box 16, Folder 129)
    - Repo History/ Greg Sholette, 1992; 206830 (Box 16, Folder 130)
    - Rhine, Arthur and Martin Silberman/ Silberman and Rhine LLD, 1998; 206831 (Box 16, Folder 131)
    - Ribé, Ángels, undated; 206832 (Box 16, Folder 132)
    - Ricardo, 2006; 206833 (Box 16, Folder 133)
    - Rice, Shelly, 1995-1996; 206834 (Box 16, Folder 134)
    - Richard, 1998; 206835 (Box 16, Folder 135)
    - Richard A, 1983; 206836 (Box 16, Folder 136)
    - Richards, Angela/ Goldsmiths University, 2001; 206837 (Box 16, Folder 137)
    - Richards, Peter, 1998; 206838 (Box 16, Folder 138)
    - Rickaby, Tony, undated; 206839 (Box 16, Folder 139)
    - Rio and Romulus, 1998; 206840 (Box 16, Folder 140)
    - Ripps, Rodney, undated; 206841 (Box 16, Folder 141)
    - Rijper-Greenidge, 1991; 206842 (Box 16, Folder 142)
    - Rish and Michael, undated; 206843 (Box 16, Folder 143)
    - Ritchie, Christina, 2001; 206844 (Box 16, Folder 144)
    - Riteway Baby Care Diaper Service, 1989; 206846 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Rob, undated; 206847 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Rob [ Tewes], 1990; 206848 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Robert, 1977; 206849 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Robert and David, undated; 206850 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Roberts, Elsie, 1985-1997; 206851 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Roberts, Linda Pace and Lawrence D. Miller, 1994; 206852 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - the children of Mr. and Mrs. Lindley Roberts, 1991-2001; 206853 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Robertson, Allan, 1987-2001; 206854 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Robillard, Rita, 1998; 206855 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Robin, 1980; 206856 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Robin and Dylan, 2004-2008, undated; 206857 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Robinson, Joyce/ Marie Walsh Sharpe Art Foundation, 2001-2002; 206858 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Rockafeller Foundation, 1987; 206859 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Rodgers, Donna, 2006; 206860 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Rodgers, John RAE, 2001; 206861 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Rodney, Lee, 1995-1996; 206862 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Rodriguez-Mora, Hiram, 1997; 206863 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Roesler, Bob, 1981-1982; 206864 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Rogan, Lindsay/ Ontario Arts Council, 1995; 206865 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Rogers, Alva and Accra Shepp, 1996-2007, undated; 206866 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Rolfe, Nigel, 1998; 206867 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Ron, 1997; 206869 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Ron and Sylvia, 2007; 206870 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Ron, Nancy Bethay and Lani, undated; 206871 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Ronald Feldman Fine Arts, undated; 206872 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Rosa, 1983; 206873 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Rosanne, 1983-1997; 206874 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Rosano, Michael, 1995; 206875 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Rose, 2001; 206876 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Rose, undated; 206877 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Rose and Sonia, undated; 206878 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Roselli, Grace, 2000-2001; 206879 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Rosen, Ann, 1995; 206880 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Rosen, Nancy, 1978; 206881 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Rosen, Randy, 1988; 206882 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Rosenberg, Barbara, 1986; 206883 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Rosengaard, Martin, 2005; 206884 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Rosenstein, Carole, 2002; 206885 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Rosenthal, Ann, 1981; 206886 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Rosenthal, Rachel, 1995; 206887 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Rosing, Larry and Nancy Saint Paul, 1984-1987; 206888 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Rosler, Martha, 1976-1977; 206889 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Ross, Marcia, 1968-1999; 206890 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Ross/Jarden Marcia, 1975-1977; 206891 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Ross, Pearl, undated; 206892 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Rossero, Robert, 1977; 206893 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Rostakowski, Alison, 2007, undated; 206894 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - the Rotanda Gallery, Nanette Rainone, Janet Riker, 1992; 206895 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Rostelanetz, Richard, 1974; 206896 (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Roth, Moira, Addressed to M.R.S., 1984-2006; 207144 (Box 17, Folder 51)